Guide to the Robert A. Caro Archive [DATE]–2021 MS 3203
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI. Scrapbooks, 1952-2021 (bulk, 1974-2020)
  - Scrapbook 22, "Master of the Senate. 5", 2002-2007, 2019 (Box [XI-16])
    [62] Advertisement for "Master of the Senate" as winner of the Pulitzer Prize, New York Times, May 1, 2003.
    [63] "Late Show Top Ten" list of "Things Never Before Said By a Pulitzer Prize Winner," presented by Robert Caro.
    [64] "New & Noteworthy Paperbacks," highlighting "Master of the Senate," New York Times, May 4, 2003.
    [65] Full-page advertisement for "Master of the Senate," New York Times Book Review, May 4, 2003.
    [66] Commencement program, C.W. Post Campus, Long Island University, May 11, 2003, at which Caro received the honorary degree of Doctor of Letters.
    [67] Certificate signed by Ernie Fletcher, Governor of Kentucky, commissioning Robert Caro a "Kentucky Colonel," November 28, 2005.
    [68] Program, Carl Sandburg Literary Award presentation to Caro, Chicago Public Library Foundation, October 9, 2003.
    [69] "How do I lead for the long haul?," Fast Company, July 2003.
    [70] Helen Dalrymple, "Robert Caro Discusses LBJ's Sources, Use of Power," The Gazette, June 20, 2003.
    [71] Hardy Green, "Summer Reading, Heavy to Light," Business Week, June 30, 2003.
    [72] Bill Cunningham, "These Joints Are Jumping," New York Times, July 13, 2003. Include photo of Ina and Robert Caro attending Friends of the High Line event on July 9.
    [73] "Robert Caro & the LBJ Library," BookTV.org, June 15, [2003].
    [74a] Postcard from Richard Hall, undated.
    [74b] "Peter Jennings Jeremiad Riles West Side Synagoguge," New York Observer, August 11, 2003.
    [74c] Mention of "Master of the Senate," in the Glasgow Herald, November 29, 2003.
    [75a] Charles Bogel, photograph of Caro signing books, May 15, 2003.
    [75b] Full-page advertisement for "Master of the Senate," The Chronicle of Higher Education, September 5, 2003.
    [76] "Caro Captures Biography Pulitzer Prize," Horace Mann Record, April 25, 2003.
    [77a] Flyer for "Caro's L.B.J. A Theatrical Portrait of the 36th President with Robert A. Caro and Friends," at the Public Theater / New York Shakespeare Festival, April 21, [2003].
    [77b] Howard Kissel, "A call for fresh ideas," New York Daily News, June 8, 2003.
    [78a] Invitation to a celebration for Robert Caro, American Jewish Historical Society, June 10, [2003].
    [78b] Carl Hulse, "From One Esteemed Corner, a Lesson About the Senate's Filibuster Rule," New York Times, June 5, 2003.
    [79] David Barboza, "An L.B.J. Feud Finally Ends. Johnson's Library and Robert Caro Make Up," New York Times, May 22, 2003.
    [80] Charles Bogel, photograph of Caro, May 13, 2003.
    [81] [blank]
    [82] Invitation from Betty Sue Flowers, Director of the LBJ Library, to a dinner following Robert Caro's presentation, May 13, [2003].
    [83] Sharyn Wizda Vade, "LBJ's library finally offers his biographer a warm welcome," Austin American-Statesman, May 14, 2003.
    [84-85] The Senate of the State of Texas, Senate Resolution No. 823, commending Robert A. Caro "for his exceptional literary contributions," May 16, 2003.
    [86] Carl Rollyson, "It Takes a City," New York Sun, December 27, 2006.
    [87] Robert A. Caro, "Turn Every Page," The New Yorker, January 28, 2019.
    [88] Full-page advertisement for "Master of the Senate," The Chronicle of Higher Education, September 5, 2003.
    [89] "Best books... chosen by Steven Brill," The Week, August 29, 2003.
    [90a] Full-page advertisement for "Master of the Senate," American Political Science Review, May 2003.
    [90b] Invitation and agenda, Theodore H. White Lecture and Seminar, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, October 28-30, 2003.
    [90c] William C. Marra, "Johnson Biographer Delivers Lecture at KSG," The Harvard Crimson, [October 29, 2003].
    [inside back cover] Telegram from Lee C. Bollinger, president, Columbia University, notifying Caro of his Pulitzer Prize, April 7, 2003.
    [inside back cover] Selection from New York Times, March 30, 2004.
    [inside back cover] Program for the 40th Annual Ernest J. & Elena A. Bruno Memorial Lecture, Lenox Hill Hospital, November 20, 2007, at which Caro delivered "The Power of Personality."
    [inside back cover] Letter from Doug Knutson, June 12, 2003.
    [inside back cover] Barton Hoexter, "Caro Kept His Hair," letter to the editor, Horace Mann, vol. 1 (2004).
    [inside back cover] Invitation, English-Speaking Union of the United States, 2004 Ambassador Book Awards, October 7, 2004, with "Citation for RAC, New York Public Library, 8 x 04."
    [inside back cover] Program, Philip and Mary Shannon Seton Hall Speaker Series, featuring Robert Caro, Thursday, October 14, [2004].
  - Scrapbook [23], 2006 (1964, 1985-1986, 2002-2020) (Box [XI-17])
    Cover embossed "2006." Contains miscellaneous topics. Note the letter from Ted Kennedy at [34].
    [01] Photographs of a group of young adults (students?) posed in an arch (at Jones Beach?), prints made January 13, 2006.
    [02a] David Patrick Columbia, "A Book Party at Le Cirque for Arnold Scaasi's 'Women I Have Dressed (And Undressed)'," QUEST, undated; includes a photograph of "Ina Caro, Parker Ladd, Robert Caro, and Barbara Taylor Bradford."
    [02b] "On The Town," New York Sun, January 20-22, 2006; includes a photograph of "Ina & Robert Caro" attending an event of the Manhattan Institute.
    [03] "Nan and the New Journalists," New York Observer, January 23, 2006.
    [04] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro at various events.
    [05] Sam Roberts, "How Government Works (Sometimes It Does," New York Times, January 22, 2006.
    [06] Norman J. Ornstein, "A Watchdog That Didn't Bark," American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, February 6, 2006.
    [07] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro at various events.
    [08] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro at various events.
    [09] "What Will History Rate Cheney? A panel of experts debates how the Vice President's power and influence—and recent mishap—will shape his legacy," TIME, February 27, 2006.
    [10] Wallace Kantai, "Go Back to the Roots," The East African Standard (Nairobi), March 27, 2006.
    [11] Invitation for the Annual Ceremonial of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, May 17, 2006.
    [12] "LBJ's power secrets," USA Today, April 3, 2006.
    [13] Roger Simon, "In death, LBJ gets his wish—image he liked," unidentified newspaper, August 30, 1985.
    [14] Front page photo of Robert Caro at the Sam Rayburn Library, The Bonham Daily Favorite, Bonham, Texas, March 13, 1986.
    [15] Crossword puzzle, New York Times, April 1, 2006. Answer to clue 27 down: "Robert who wrote 'The Power Broker'" (Caro).
    [16] Printout of photograph of Caro (at Sam Rayburn Library?), April 20, 2006.
    [17] Jennifer Schuessler, "Robert Caro's Papers Headed to New-York Historical Society," New York Times, January 8, 2020 (partial printout).
    [18a] Photograph of Robert and Ina Caro with a group.
    [18b] Program for the New York Times' "Times Talks" featuring Robert Caro on "Power & Process," April 9, 2019.
    [19] Mockup of photograph of the Caros sitting on their car in Texas that accompanied New Yorker article, October, 2015.
    [20] Photograph of "Robert Caro in his office in Manhattan this month" that accompanied Jennifer Schuessler's "Robert Caro's Papers Headed to New-York Historical Society," New York Times, January 8, 2020.
    [21] Joel Conarroe's remarks on presenting to Robert Caro the gold medal for biography of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, May 17, 2006.
    [22] Letter from Francesca Stanfill to Ina Caro, January 1, 2012.
    [23] List of American Academy of Arts and Letters new members and 2006 award recipients, New York Times, May 18, 2006.
    [24] Jonathan Weber, "Why books resist the rise of novel technologies," Times Online (www.timesonline.co.uk), May 24, 2006.
    [25] Email exchange regarding "The Power Broker" between Deborah Sinclaire of Doubleday, Sean Yule of Random House, and Katherine Hourigan, November 17-22, 2006.
    [26a] "Best books... chosen by Jonathan Alter," The Week, July 5-12, 2013.
    [26b] Email from Thomas Dobrowolski regarding Bookspan's promotion of "The Power Broker."
    [27] Robert A. Caro, "Anatomy of a $9 Burglary," Newsday, June 13, 1964.
    [28] Smithsonian, May 2012. Partial issue containing fragment of an interview with Caro.
    [29] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro, and of Robert Caro promoting his book "Working."
    [30] Mockup of cover of Francis Parkman Prize Edition of "The Power Broker," issued by the History Book Club.
    [31a] Letter from David P. Cross, November 9, 2006.
    [31b] Photographs of Robert Caro posed with "auction winners."
    [32] "Alumni Honored with Prestigious Arts Awards," Horace Mann Magazine, vol. 2, no. 2 (Fall 2006).
    [33] Lynn Haraldson-Bering, "Been There, Done That," The Clarion News, [June 14, 2006].
    [34] Letter from Edward M. "Ted" Kennedy, November 1, [2004?], thanking Caro for his participation in the Edward M. Kennedy Oral History Project, which launched December 6, 2004.
    [35] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro in various settings.
    [36] Photographs of Robert and Ina Caro in various settings.
    [37] Stacy Sullivan, "Burning Love," Op-Ed, New York Times, March 19, 2006.
    [38a] New York Society Library Notes, vol. 13, no. 1 (Winter 2006), listing Caro's appearance during the 2005-2006 Author Series (March 15, 2006).
    [38b] Brochure, "Author Series, 2005-2006," Thirteen/WNET, listing Caro's appearance, March 15, 2006.
    [39a] Photograph of Robert Caro with New York Times editor Arthur Gelb and columnist Maureen Dowd, April 24, 2006.
    [39b] Partial report of the funeral of New York Times executive editor A. M. Rosenthal, New York Sun, May 14, 2006; includes a photograph of Robert Caro with Joseph Lelyveld.
    [39c] Photograph of Robert Caro with executive chef from Des Artistes, May 14, 2006.
    [40] Horace Mann Magazine, vol. 2, no. 1 (Spring 2006); includes a report on Caro, class of 1953.
    [41] Email from Robert Weil to Ina and Robert Caro regarding the 10th paperback printing of Ina's book "Paris to the Past," April 5, 2017.
    [42a] Program for the Annual Ceremonial of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, May 17, 2006.
    [42b] Nametag: "Robert Caro / Gold Medal for Biography."
    [42c] Photographs of Robert Caro and another man, presumably at the same event.
    [43] Daniel Finkelstein, "Is this the greatest biography of our era?," The Times (London), April 25, 2002.
    [44] Photograph of Robert Caro and an unidentified woman.
    [45a] "Various Reviews from Great Britain," April 4, 2012.
    [45b] Daniel Finkelstein, "To lie, cheat and betray and still do some good," The Times (London), [date missing].
    [46] William Hague, "The perfect personality for politics," Sunday Telegraph (London), August 4, 2002.
    [47] Daniel Hannan, "The best biography ever written," Telegraph.co.uk, February 13, 2008.
    [48a] Vintage photographs of Ina Caro and Robert Caro with son, Chase.
    [48b] Photograph of Robert Caro with unidentified people by Amelia V. Panico.
    [49] Photograph of "A file folder holding transcripts of interviews" that accompanied Jennifer Schuessler's "Robert Caro's Papers Headed to New-York Historical Society," New York Times, January 8, 2020.
    [50] Photograph of "A page from one of Mr. Caro's reporting notebooks" that accompanied Jennifer Schuessler's "Robert Caro's Papers Headed to New-York Historical Society," New York Times, January 8, 2020.
    [51] [blank]
    [52] Itinerary for Caro's presentation, "Fifty Years Ago Tomorrow: John F. Kennedy, Lyndon Johnson, and November 22, 1963," at the New-York Historical Society, November 21, 2013.
    [53] Caro's submission to "When We Were Young: Childhood in New York," which ran in New York Magazine's annual Yesteryear Issue, April 8, 2013.
    [54-55] Photographs of the Caros in various locales in France.
    [56-59] Photographs of Robert Caro at an award ceremorny.
    [60a] Photograph of Ina Caro with two women.
    [60b] Christmas card inscribed to "Bob and Ina" with a photo of the Caros affixed.
    [60c] Partial wrapper from The New Yorker with the words "Power Broker" circled, date missing.
    [61a] Photograph of Ina Caro in France.
    [61b] Photocopy of a photograph of [Ina Caro?].
    [62] Photographs of the Caros in France.
    [63a] Photograph of the Caros outside a travel agency.
    [63b] Photographs of Ina Caro at a gathering.
    [64] David Zurawik, "'Loudest Voice'—Judging Roger Ailes with no sense of history," Baltimore Sun, January 17, 2014.
    [65a] "Best books... chosen by Rosie Perez," The Week, March 7, 2014.
    [65b] Photograph of Robert Caro with Bill Clinton.
    [67-69] Anne Hull, "Master of the Craft," Nieman Reports, vol. 68, no. 1 (Winter 2014).
    [70] Julie Bosman, "Literary City, Bookstore Desert," New York Times, March 26, 2014.
    [71] Patrick Beach, "Research delights LBJ biographer," Austin American-Statesman, April 6, 2014.
    [72-73] Jesse Caro, "EDGE interview, Robert A. Caro," Edge Magazine, date missing.
    [74] Dwight Garner, "Lost in Literary History: A Tale of Courage in the South," New York Times, April 19, 2014.
    [75] Photocopy of a photograph of Robert Caro.
    [76a] Letter to Ina Caro from Ana Luiza Calabria, July 17, 2013.
    [76b] Note to Ina Caro from Lisbeth Bond, undated.
    [77] Letter to Ina Caro from Lisbeth Bond, July 27, 2013.
    [78a] Printouts of photographs of the Caros, April 25, 2014.
    [78b] Photographs of the Caros at a gathering.
    [79a] Program for Caro's talk "The Years of Lyndon Johnson: The Passage of Power," at Wallace Hall, the Church of St. Ignatius Loyola, [late 2012?].
    [79b] Tear sheet from an unidentified periodical displaying the ten most popular nonfiction books, of which "Passage of Power" is number 2.
    [80] Brennan Center for Justice at New York University School of Law, Newsletter, July 2014; photo captioned "Michael Waldman, Mark Green, Robert A. Caro, and Ina Caro celebrate the publication of [Waldman's] 'The Second Amendment: A Biography'."
    [81] Sarah Gordon, "Lunch with the FT Robert Caro / The power and the story," Financial Times, London, January 5-6, 2013.
    [82] [blank]
    [83a] Invitation, "David Wolkowsky Request [sic] Your Presence At a Drinks Party for Robert A. Caro," January 13, 2017.
    [83b] Partial program for the 35th Annual Key West Literary Seminar, January 12-15, 2017.
    [84a] Parul Sehgal, "Queens Expire, Haunting a Fixer," New York Times, March 3, 2020.
    [84b] Christoper Bonanos, "The 'New York' Magazine Competition," New York Magazine, June 16-29, 2014. Instructions for "Competition No. 24: First Reactions" asks contestants to "Please suggest the initial remarks on a major occasions made by a note figure. For example: 'How many pages do you think it'll be?'—Robert Gottlieb, to Robert Caro."
    [84c] Photographs of the Caros at gatherings.
    [85] Compiled reviews of "Passage of Power," February 24, 2014.
    [86] Patrick Beach, "LBJ biographer nearing end of story," statesman.com, May 26, 2012.
    [87] Anne Hull, "Master of the Craft," Nieman Reports, vol. 68, no. 1 (Winter 2014).
    [88] Horace Mann Magazine, vol. 8, no. 1 (Spring 2014); news of Caro in report of class of 1953.
    [89] Charles McGrath, "Robert Caro is a Dinosaur. And thank God for that," New York Times Magazine, April 15, 2012.
    [90] Photograph of a boy reading "The Power Broker."
  - Scrapbook [24], 2007-2009 (+1955) (Box [XI-18])
    Cover embossed "2007." Contains miscellaneous topics.
    [01] Advertisement for paperback edition of Power Broker.
    [02] Contact sheet of 108 jpg thumbnails of Caro speaking at the Gerald R. Ford Museum.
    [03] "New York architecture. Calling Mr. Caro. As New York re-evaluates Robert Moses, his biographer weighs in," The Economist, February 17-23, 2007.
    [04] "It's never time for another Robert Moses, says Caro," New York Observer, February 19, 2007.
    [05] HistoryBookClub.com publication announcing the Francis Parkman Prize Edition of The Power Broker, February 2007.
    [06] "Robert Moses and the Modern City," exhibition listing, New Yorker, March 5, 2007.
    [07] "Lessons in Power: Lyndon Johnson Revealed. A Conversation with Historian Robert A. Caro," Harvard Business Review (reprint), April 2006 [2 copies].
    [09] Advertisement for paperback edition of Power Broker, New York Times, January 31, 2007.
    [10] Philip Kennicott, "A Builder Who Went to Town," Washington Post, March 11, 2007.
    [11] Ada Louise Huxtable, "Shows Try to Renovate Moses' Reputation," Wall Street Journal, March 14, 2007.
    [12] Photo of Caro at Academy of American Poets gala at Avery Fisher Hall as published in newyorksocialdiary.com, April 4, 2008.
    [13] Liz Smith, "Poetry worth 1,000 pictures," New York Post, April 6, 2008.
    [14] Letter from Thomas G. Wicker, May 7, 2008.
    [15] Sam Anderson, "The New York Canon. Books, from Norman Mailer to Rem Koolhaas, 26 works of lapidary New Yorkitude," New York Magazine, April 14, 2008.
    [16] "Best books... chosen by Steven Waldman," The Week, June 6, 2008.
    [17] Tunku Varadarajan, "The Politician as Biographer. A Cultural Conversation with William Hague," Wall Street Journal, June 4, 2008.
    [18a] Letter from Jan Hughes and Heidi Marquez Smith, inviting Caro to be honored at the Texas Book Festival, June 18, 2008.
    [18b] Email from Stephen Harrigan informing Caro of his impending honor by the Texas Book Festival, June 18, 2008.
    [19]Tunku Varadarajan, "The Politician as Biographer. A Cultural Conversation with William Hague," Wall Street Journal, June 4, 2008.
    [20a] "Celebrating New York's Color, Characters, and Leaders," New York Sun, September 10, 2008.
    [20b] Program, The Rockefeller Foundation Jane Jacobs Medal 2008 Awards Dinner, listing Caro's speech "Jane Jacobs, "RM' and the Future of New York City."
    [21] Invitation to New-York Historical Society 2008 History Makers Gala honoring Robert A. Caro and Jack Rudin and the Rudin Family [2 pieces].
    [22] Letter from Jan Hughes and Heidi Marquez Smith, inviting Caro to be honored at the Texas Book Festival, June 18, 2008.
    [23a] Jill Abramson, "The Final Days," New York Times Book Review, September 28, 2008.
    [23b] "News about Robert A. Caro, including commentary and archival articles published in The New York Times," 1987-2007.
    [24] "The Approval Matrix (Anniversary Edition)," New York Magazine, October 6, 2008.
    [25] Photographs of the Caros traveling in France.
    [26-28] Photographs of Caro at a State University of New York, Stony Brook, event.
    [29] Robert A. Caro, "Johnson's Dream, Obama's Speech," New York Times Op-Ed, August 28, 2008.
    [30a] Letter from Theodore C. Rogers, October 20, 2008.
    [30b] Note from Francine Klagsburn, October, 20, 2008.
    [30c] Photographs of the Caros with a young woman.
    [31] Invitation to New-York Historical Society 2008 History Makers Gala honoring Robert A. Caro and Jack Rudin and the Rudin Family [3 copies].
    [32] Program for New-York Historical Society 2008 History Makers Gala [2 copies].
    [33a] Note from "Ed & Nancy" [Sorel] on recto of an Edward Sorel cartoon of a begging Uncle Sam wearing a placard reading "Lost My Country. Please Give What You Can," December 2007.
    [33b] Letter from David A. Paterson, Governor of the State of New York, to honorees of the New-York Historical Society 2008 History Makers Gala, October 15, 2008.
    [34a] "Book festival draws acclaimed and emerging," editorial, Austin American-Statesman, October 31, 2008.
    [34b] Invitation for a "Sunday Brunch" hosted by the Austin Public Library, featuring Robert Caro and other nationally renowned authors, November 2, 2008.
    [35a] "The Texas Book Festival Honors Author Robert Caro" (press release), October 30, 2008.
    [35b] Texas Book Festival program information. On one, Caro(?) has written a quote from St. Augustine: "The world is a book & those that do no travel read only a page."
    [36] Patrick Beach and Jeff Salamon, "Biographer honored where LBJ once stood," Austin American-Statesman, November 3, 2008 [copy 1].
    [37a] Patrick Beach and Jeff Salamon, "Biographer honored where LBJ once stood," Austin American-Statesman, November 3, 2008 [copy 2].
    [37b] Texas Book Festival passes for "Robert Caro, Author" and "Ina Caro, Panelist," November 1-2, 2008.
    [38] Max Abelson, "Ted Sorensen Hosts Robert Caro, Other Luminaries Tonight at 15 CPW," New York Observer, November 4, 2008.
    [39] New York Observer, November 10, 2008. Tear sheets chronicling how New York City watched the presidential election returns.
    [40] Email from Tina Washington Bristol, "The Passing of Aaron Sellers," November 6, 2008.
    [41] Invitation, The New York Public Library Council of Conservators, "Privileged Information: A Look at the Oval Office through the Historian's Prism, featuring special guests Robert Caro, Bob Clark, Ted Sorenson," October 21, 2008.
    [42-43] Photographs of Caro at a State University of New York, Stony Brook, event.
    [44] Photographs of the Caros with a young man and woman.
    [45] Wendy Smith, "Historical Books: The Path to Power (The Years of Lyndon Johnson, Volume 1), bookshistorical.blogspot.com, November 26, 2008.
    [46] Email from David Williams, December 4, 2008, attaching a review he wrote of "Master of the Senate" for the Johannesburg Financial Mail, February 13, 2004.
    [47a] Kate Ward, "Writers at Work," Entertainment Weekly, December 5, 2008.
    [47b] Photograph of Caro's office desk, November 2008.
    [48] New-York Historical Society "Programs & Exhibitions," Fall 2008 / Winter 2009, listing "Robert A. Caro on the Shapers of New York," January 14, 21, and 28, 2009.
    [49] Flier for "Robert A. Caro on 'The Shapers of New York'," New-York Historical Society, January 14, 21, and 28, 2009.
    [50] Photocopy of Caro's piece "Morris Bucks for Winning Touchdown As Penn Goal-Line Stands Slow Tigers" in The Daily Princetonian, October 10, 1955.
    [51] Flier for the Bronxville Historical Conservancy's 10th Annual Brendan Gill Lecture, featuring Robert Caro, February 8, 2008.
    [52] Humorous letter from Tom Foerster inquiring on when the next installment of Caro's LBJ biography would be out.
    [53] Jonathan Darman, "The Marathon Man. Robert Caro spent decades living LBJ's life. His goal with the last volume is the same as it was with the first: to endure," Newsweek, February 16, 2009 [2 copies].
    [54-55] Jonathan Darman, "The Marathon Man. Robert Caro spent decades living LBJ's life. His goal with the last volume is the same as it was with the first: to endure," Newsweek, February 16, 2009. With a card enclosing the same from Vartan Gregorian, President, Carnegie Corporation of New York.
    [56-57] Photographs of the Caros at an awards ceremony and book signing (likely the Texas Book Festival, November 2008).
    [58] Dwight Garner, "Piecing Together That Voice on the Barroom Floor," New York Times, May 20, 2009.
    [59] Note from "Dick," Senate Historian Dr. Richard A. Baker, thanking Caro for remarks on his retirement, August 19, 2009.
    [60] Invitation and program, "Poets & Writers, In Celebration of Writers, "Honoring Russell Banks, Robert Caro, Sarah Gambito, Daniel Halpern," Gala Benefit Dinner, March 25, 2009.
    [62] Sun Valley Writers' Conference, program and booklet, August 22-25, 2008. Both Robert and Ina Caro participated.
    [inside back cover] Invitations to the 2009 Leon Levy Biography Lecture, given by Robert A. Caro, September 29, 2009, and the following dinner honoring Caro.
  - Scrapbook [25] [no identification], 2009-2014 (+1991) (Box [XI-19])